dmarcian.com 2013-08-08

# dmarcian - DMARC Tools For Humans

    13 January 2013 - update to indicate user-submitted data gets deleted when account is deleted
    24 February 2012 - original publication

The privacy and security of personal information is a dmarcian.com priority, and we want you to be aware of how your information is collected and handled.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of dmarcian.com on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on http://dmarcian.com (the "Site") and the services, features, content or applications offered by dmarcian.com (collectively with the Site, the "Services"). dmarcian.com receives information about you from your use of the Services generally. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## What information is collected?

User-submitted Content
    dmarcian.com collects information submitted by users such as DMARC XML aggregate files and information pertaining to the submission such as source IP address of submissions and time of submission. All content submitted anonymously (without being logged into the Services) may be retained by dmarcian.com indefinitely, even after you stop using the Services. All content submitted by you while logged into the Services may be retained by dmarcian.com until account deletion. Account deletion removes all content that was submitted to the Services while logged into the account.
IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically
    dmarcian.com automatically receives and records information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address and cookie information. This information may be used to help dmarcian.com understand how users transit the Site, to fight spam/malware, to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services and for other similar purposes.  
Generally, the Services automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. dmarcian.com may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a way that would identify you personally. This ttype of aggregate data enables dmarcian.com to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that dmarcian.com can analyze and improve them.
Email Communications
    dmarcian.com collects email addresses and email communications from users to support the Services. dmarcian.com does not disclose email addresses to third parties, and does not send email to users on matters outside of the scope of the Services.

## How is collected information used?

Human-friendly Reports
    Information collected by dmarcian.com is used to generate human- friendly DMARC XML reports. Human-friendly reports are made available through obfuscated URLs that can be shared by the submitter with other users. dmarcian.com does not share obfuscated URLs with third parties, but users are free to do so.
Metrics and Analysis
    dmarcian.com may use site statistics (such as clicks, navigation, and webserver logs) to improve the dmarcian.com website.
Email Correspondence
    Email communications made to dmarcian.com are never shared by dmarcian.com with parties outside of dmarcian.com. Email addresses are not harvested, sold, or otherwise made available to third parties. dmarcian.com only uses email addresses for direct correspondence with users and for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery.
Information Disclosed for the Protection of dmarcian.com and Others
    dmarcian.com also reserves the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iii) respond to user support requests, or (iv) protect the rights, property or safety of dmarcian.com, its users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention. 

## How can collected information be shared?

Human-friendly Reports
    Human-friendly reports are made available through obfuscated URLs that can be shared by the submitter with other users. dmarcian.com does not share obfuscated URLs with third parties, but users are free to do so.
ECPA NOTICE
    dmarcian.com treats email messages and other communications through this site (except for email messages posted to areas of this site that are viewable by others) as private. Exceptions are those permitted by law, included under the Electronic Communications Privacy Act of 1986, 18 U.S.C. Sections 2701-2711 (the "ECPA"). The ECPA permits our limited ability to intercept and/or disclose electronic messages, including, for example (i) as necessary to operate our system or to protect our rights or property, (ii) upon legal demand (court orders, warrants, subpoenas), or (iii) where we receive information inadvertently which appears to pertain to the commission of a crime. This site is not considered a "secure communications medium" under the ECPA.

## Disclosures

External Links
    The Site may contain links to other websites. dmarcian.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Compliance with Email Communication Laws
    dmarcian.com supports and complies with all laws governing its email communications and will update this policy as needed to ensure ongoing compliance. 
Change in Privacy Policy
    dmarcian.com reserves the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy. dmarcian.com will provide notice of such changes by posting at: http://dmarcian.com/privacy.html. Users not agreeing to the modified Privacy Policy may stop the use of the Service. Continued use after such modifications have been posted shall be deemed acceptance of by user.

For questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
